Welcome to the Bajaj Allianz Health Guard Policy overview.
This health insurance plan offers a comprehensive range of benefits designed to protect you from major medical expenses related to illness or accidents.
With affordable coverage options,
Bajaj Allianz prioritizes your health and financial security.
The Health Guard Policy offers three tailor-made plans: Silver,
Gold,
and Platinum.
Each plan is designed to meet your health care needs,
providing you with options that ensure comprehensive coverage.
In the Silver Plan,
you can choose sums insured of Rs.
1.
5 or 2 lacs.
For the Gold Plan,
options range from Rs.
3 lacs up to a maximum of Rs.
50 lacs.
Lastly,
the Platinum Plan offers a wider range,
from Rs.
5 lacs to Rs.
1 Crore,
ensuring ample coverage for various health care needs.
The Health Guard Policy accepts proposers and their family members from 18 years up to a lifelong age limit.
Dependent children can be insured from the age of 3 months to 30 years.
Importantly,
the policy supports lifetime renewals under normal circumstances.
You have the flexibility to choose a policy period of 1,
2,
or 3 years.
Premium payments can be made annually,
half-yearly,
quarterly,
or monthly.
This allows you to manage your insurance expenses according to your budget.
Key benefits include coverage for in-patient hospitalization,
road ambulance costs,
organ donor expenses,
and maternity expenses.
Additional features such as preventive health check-ups and convalescence benefits are also provided,
ensuring a well-rounded coverage.
Depending on the chosen premium payment zone,
you may incur co-payments for treatments.
Zone A provides the best coverage without co-payments,
while Zones B and C may involve co-payment percentages based on hospital location.
Understanding the exclusions is crucial.
The policy does not cover pre-existing conditions for the first 36 months,
specific diseases for 24 months,
and any treatments falling under the exclusions listed in the policy documentation.
The claims process is straightforward.
For empaneled hospitals,
present your cashless card.
For non-empaneled hospitals,
make payments upfront and submit a claim along with the necessary documentation for reimbursement.
To purchase the Bajaj Allianz Health Guard Policy,
discuss options with an insurance advisor or visit the Bajaj Allianz website.
For any queries or assistance,
you can reach out to the toll-free numbers or email the support team for timely help.